const britquestions = [{
        id: 1,
        question: "What was Britney Spears' first single?",
        answers: ["Baby One More Time", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "Toxic", "Womanizer"],
        correctAnswer: "Baby One More Time"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What was Britney Spears' debut album?",
        answers: ["Britney", "Britney Jean", "Britney Baby One More Time", "Britney Speared"],
        correctAnswer: "Britney Baby One More Time"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What was Britney Spears' highest charting single on the Billboard Hot 100?",
        answers: ["Baby One More Time", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "Toxic", "Womanizer"],
        correctAnswer: "Toxic"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What was the title of Britney Spears' first music video?",
        answers: ["Baby One More Time", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "Toxic", "Womanizer"],
        correctAnswer: "Baby One More Time"
    },
    {
    id: 5,
        question: "What is the title of Britney Spears' ninth studio album?",
        answers: ["Britney Jean", "Britney Baby One More Time", "Britney Speared", "Glory"],
        correctAnswer: "Glory"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What was the title of Britney Spears' first world tour?",
        answers: ["Oops!...I Did It Again Tour", "Britney Live in Concert", "Baby One More Time Tour", "Dream Within a Dream Tour"],
        correctAnswer: "Baby One More Time Tour"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Britney Spears has won how many Grammy Awards?",
        answers: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "1"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "In which year did Britney Spears make her acting debut in the film 'Crossroads'?",
        answers: ["1998", "2000", "2002", "2004"],
        correctAnswer: "2002"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What was the title of Britney Spears' first perfume?",
        answers: ["Curious", "Fantasy", "Midnight Fantasy", "Radiance"],
        correctAnswer: "Curious"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What was the title of Britney Spears' reality TV show?",
        answers: ["Britney and Kevin: Chaotic", "Britney: For the Record", "Britney: Live and More", "Britney: Unbreakable"],
        correctAnswer: "Britney and Kevin: Chaotic"
    }
    ];

    module.exports = { britquestions };